Guide to the Sol Gorelick Papers WAG.019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Labor and Unions, 2
  - Workers Action Movement (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Work Study - RESTRICTED (Box 18, Folder 1)
- National Association of Social Workers, 3
  The National Association of Social Workers (NASW) is a professional organization for social workers in the United States. It was founded in 1955.
  Sol Gorelick was active in the in the NASW's New York City Chapter. He served on several committees, including the Executive Committee and the Welfare Policy Committee, for which he was chair.
  This series documents Gorelick's activities in the professional organization the National Association of Social Workers. The bulk of the documents date from the mid-1970s to early 1980s. Gorelick was active in the NASW's New York City Chapter, and the majority of the series pertains to chapter activities.
  Lobbying activities of the national organization and New York City Chapter are represented in folders for the Education Legislative Action Network (ELAN). Gorelick was chair of the Welfare Policy Committee, and the committee's activities are well-documented. There are minutes for meetings of the chapter's Welfare Policy Committee, Executive Committee, and Board of Directors, among other groups. Publications present include the national organization's Advocate for Human Services, the New York City Chapter's newsletter Currents, and ELAN's ELAN Alert. The series also contains correspondence, documentation of planning activities for conferences, fliers, pamphlets, and policy statements. Gorelick's professional organization interests often overlapped with union activity and employment with the city. This series illustrates how activism and public policy concerns found outlets across different spheres.
  - National Association of Social Workers (Box 9, Folder 1-14)
  - Advocacy Conference (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Advocate for Human Services (National Newsletter) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Chapter Task Force to Restructure the Social Services of New York City (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action Committee - Task Force on Racism (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME, District Coucil 37 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors (NYC Chapter) (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
  - Board of Directors Meetings (NYC Chapter) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - National Association of Social Workers - Chapter Action Guide, Program Planning (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Chapter Directory (NYC Chapter) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Chapter Officers' Meetings (NYC Chapter) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Conferences and Seminars (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Welfare Policy Committee and Creative Arts Rehabilitation Center (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with City Officials and Politicians (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Currents (New York Chapter Newsletter) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Delegate Assembly (Box 9, Folder 30-31)
  - Delegate Assembly - Policy Statements and Resolutions (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Delegate Assembly (Policy, Program Outlines, Etc.) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Eastern Regional Meeting - Minutes (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Eastern Regional Coalition - Minutes, Policy Proposals, Etc. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - ELAN Alert (Newsletter from ELAN Center, NASW Legislative Department) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Education Legislative Action Network (ELAN) - Lobbying Day Materials (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Educational Legislative Action Network (ELAN) - Meetings (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Educational Legislative Action Network (ELAN) - Position Bulletins and Resolutions (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Elections (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Executive Committee (NYC Chapter) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Meetings - Open Membership, Public, International Committee (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Health Committee (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Helen G. Fooner Memorial Lecture Series (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Housing Committee - Welfare, Rents (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Joint Meeting with American Orthopsychiatric Association (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Legislative Day Evaluation Forms (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Membership Analysis - Response to National Office (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Memorial Service for Phyllis Hersh, Chair of Peace and Social Welfare Committee (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - NASW Newsletter (New York State Chapter) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Peace and Social Welfare Committee (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Position Paper on Welfare Housing and Rents (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Position Statements (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Position Statements: Compilation of Social Policy Statements (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Preparatory Material for Delegate Assembly - Intra-organizational, Professional, and Public Policy Issues (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Program Committee - Program Priority Selection (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Mercer - "Proposal for Restructuring Public Social Services in NYC," (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Restricted Payments to AFDC Recipients (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Draft Letter to the Research Council (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Settlement Housing Fund, Inc. - RESTRICTED (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Shaping the Future for the 1980s (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Testimony at the Public Forum Conducted by New York State Department of Social Services and New York City Department of Human Resources (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Testimony before the Welfare Refrom Subcommittee of US House of Representatives (H.R. 9030) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Testimony by Chapter President Georgia McMurray at Human Resources Administration Public Hearing on Child Abuse (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Welfare Grant Increase Coalition (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Policy Committee (Box 10, Folder 16-18)
  - Welfare Policy Committee - Campaign for the Removal of Blanche Burnstein, Commissoner of New York State Department of Social Services (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Policy Committee - City and State Government officials - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Policy Committee - Meeting Minutes (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Welfare Policy Committee - Position Statements and Resolutions (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Welfare Policy Committee - Task Force on the Urban Crisis (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Welfare Task Force (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Year in Review Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Organizations and Subjects, 4
  Gorelick's involvement in community work and engagement with progressive causes went beyond his professional and union activities. This series documents additional organizations and subjects that Gorelick was involved with or monitored. Types include neighborhood and community organizations, social work professional organizations, nonprofit social service organizations, health and healthcare, politics, peace, and education.
  The Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association is particularly well represented. Gorelick was active in the leadership of the organization, and served as secretary and president. Materials are mostly from the 1970s and encompass the full range of organizational and informational documents, including correspondence, pamphlets, the In Short monthly newsletter, meeting minutes, audits, clippings, and documents from other organizations concerned with eliminating tuberculosis and smoking.
  A notable amount of material documents activism in the United States opposed to Augusto Pinochet's 1973 coup in Chile. Social workers' professional organizations, unions, and groups throughout the left advocated for intervention to prevent human rights abuses. These materials contain publications, clippings, correspondence, and other material from groups concerned with the situation in Chile.
  - Abortion (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for a New Progressive Social Work Organization (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Addresses (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Adelphi University - Correspondence, Transcripts for Sol Gorelick (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Adelphi University Alumni Association (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Adelphi University - Syllabi and Coursework (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - American Lung Association (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - American Lung Association - "Basic Documents" (Agreement, Policy and Guidelines Manual) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - American Lung Association Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - American Lung Association: 75th Anniversary Celebration Committee (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - American Lung Association: Symposium on Occupational Hazards to the Lungs (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - American Public Welfare Association (Box 10, Folder 37-43)
  - American Public Welfare Association (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Americans Against Union Control of Government (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Nuclear Rally (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Association for National Welfare Reform: Self-help Guide for the Poor on Social Services and Public Assistance in New York City (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Association of Neighborhood Councils (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Big Business Day (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Black Hills International Survival Gathering (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Black Panther Party (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bread for New York (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Committee of One Thousand (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Ethical Meeting House (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn Independent Voters Association (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn People's Action Conference (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association (Box 11, Folder 16-31)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Allied Health Professionals Symposium (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Disease - Annual Meeting (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Board of Directors (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Brooklyn Breathing Partners (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Brooklyn Lung Center Development Committee (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Budget (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Buildings (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Clippings (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Committee to Evaluate the Executive Director (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Committees and Committee Changes (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Community Health Advisory Committee (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Consumer Commission on the Accreditation of Health Services - Medical Technology and the Healthcare Consumer Conference (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Constituent Relations Committee (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Correspondence to Congressman Brasco (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Correspondence with Managing Director Anthony Vera (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Correspondence with Vice President Anthony Mauro (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Executive Committee (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Finance Committee (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Fund Raising Committee (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - In Short newsletter (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Legislative Committee (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Long-range Planning Committee (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Luncheon Meeting Minutes (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Media Coverage (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Medical Advisory committee (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - National Conference of Executives (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Nominating Committee (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Nursing Committee (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Forum: The Psycho-Social Needs of the Chronic Lung Disease Patient (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Pamphlets and Publications (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Publications (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Program of Work (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Seminars (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Social Work Advisory Committee (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Brooklyn Tuberculosis and Lung Association - Tuberculosis Management (Bureau of Tuberculosis, Department of Health, City of New York) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Brownsville Community Council (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Brownsville Consumers Cooperative Society (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Brownsville Council for Social Planning - A Study of the Recreational Facilities of the Brownsville Section of Brooklyn (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Brownsville Boys' Club (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Brownsville Council (Committee) on Youth (Box 12, Folder 44-47)
  - Brownsville Improvement Group (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Brownsville Neighborhood Health and Welfare Council (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Canadian Welfare (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Canarsie Youth Center - Still Life (Youth Art Journal) (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Catalyst (Socialist Journal of the Social Services) - Press Release (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Catholic Home Bureau (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Center for Defense Information (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Center on Social Welfare, Policy and Law (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Center on Social Welfare, Policy and Law - Application Process for AFDC Benefits - Correspondence with NASW (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Central Brooklyn Mobilization (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Central Brooklyn Talent Search Community Calendar (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Chama Society (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Channel 13 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Chile (Box 12, Folder 62-65)
  - Chile (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
  - Chile Informative (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Chile - Maryann Mahaffey's Material on her Visit to Chile (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Chile - Newspaper Clippings (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Chile - United Nations General Assemby Reports (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Citizens Against Increases Now (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Citizens' Committee for Governmental Planning (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Citizens Party (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Citywide Coalition to Save Our Hospitals (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Citywide Coordinating Committee of Welfare Groups (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Citywide Health Professionals Association (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Civil Rights (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Civil Service Merit Council (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Client-Worker Alliance (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Clippings (Box 13, Folder 20-24)
  - Clippings - Health and Hospitals (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Clippings - "How They Wrecked the Welfare Department" (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Clippings - Welfare (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Richard Cloward (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy - letter (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Coalition for Full Employment (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Coalition on the Economic Crisis (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Coalition to Fight for Meaningful Jobs - Fight for Jobs Conference (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Columbia University School of Social Work (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Committee for a Negro Congressman from Brooklyn (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Committee for the Fund for Milton Cohen vs HUAC (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Committee for Independent Political Action (CIPA) - Greenwich Village (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Committee of the Professions - Social Workers for Peace (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Committee to Defend Imani (Johnny Harris) and Stop the Death Penalty (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Committee to Defend Poor and Working People Against Repression - Security Brutality in Jamaica welfare (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Committee to Elect Communist Candidates - "The Electric Shock: Con Ed's Billion Dollar Swindle" (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Committee to Save the 35 Cent Fare (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Committee Action for Legal Services (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Community Council of Greater New York (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Ad-Hoc Committee on Project State Levels of AFDC and Home Relief (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Community Council of Great New York - An Alternative to the Welfare Check (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Better Times: Health and Welfare Weekly Newspaper (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Conference on Welfare Advocacy (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Face to Face Recertification Citizens Monitoring Committee (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Human Services Advocacy Center (Proposal) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Community Council for Greater New York - Income Maintenance Task Force (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Community Council for Greater New York - Meeting Regarding Unemployed Minors Stricken from Home Relief Rolls (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Network Newsletter (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Research Utilization Update on Income Maintenance Research for Public Policy (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Task Force on the NYC Crisis (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Task Force on Welfare Issues, Public Assistance Inflation Adjustment (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Title XX: The State Plan Conference (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Community Council of Greater New York - Welfare Grant Increase Coalition (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Community Service Society (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Community Service Society - Conference on Welfare Advocacy (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Concered Citizens Committee on Africa (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Conflict Resolution (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Consumer Health Advocacy Committee (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Contact Citywide Coordinating Committee on Welfare Groups - Request for Fair Hearing Sample Letter (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Coordinating Council for Amending the McCarran-Walter Act (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - Appeal to Assmblyman Regarding Inflation Relief (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - General (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Council on Municipal Reform (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Council of Lung Associations of New York (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - CQ Weekly Report (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Credit Unions (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Crown Heights (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Cuba - Travel Program (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Cultural events, including Molly Maguire and Sacco and Vanzetti (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Datebooks (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Democratic Party (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Direct Action for Rights and Employment (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Disarmament (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Downtown Welfare Advocate Center (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Downtown Welfare Advocate Center - Redistribute America Movement (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - East Flatbush Neighborhood Action Program (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - East New York (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Education (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - El Salvador (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Ethnic Neighborhood Action Center - Up With Neighborhoods (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Federal Welfare Reform Proposals (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Fiscal Crisis Committee (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Food Stamps and Food Distribution (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Rae Glauber (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Gray Panthers (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - The Greater New York Fund - United Way (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Health and Healthcare (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Health Education Council of Brooklyn (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Hong Kong (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Handwritten Chronology of Welfare and Labor-related Events (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Idea Forum (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - In-Rem Tenants Coalition (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Institute on Pluralism and Group Identity (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - International Council on Social Welfare (Box 14, Folder 59-60)
  - International Federation of Social Workers - Missing Chilean Social Workers (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Interracial Home Visit with White Families/Brooklyn Home Visit Day (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Jewish Examiner (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Jewish Organizations and Culture (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Jewish War Veterans (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Joint Economic Committee (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Karen Silkwood Fund (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Labor Management Institute of the American Arbitration Association: Memorandum on Municipal Collective Bargaining (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Marin County Department of Public Social Services (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Marxism (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - May Day (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Michael Schwerner Memorial Fund (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Brooklyn Times (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Mobilization for Survival (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Movement for Economic Justice (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Multi-Service Center #1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National Coalition for Economic Justice (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - National Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - National Committee on Fraternities in Education (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - National Conference on Social Welfare (Box 15, Folder 17-18)
  - National Conference on Social Welfare - Cincinnati (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Conference on Social Welfare - Daily Bulletin (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - National Conference on Social Welfare - Presentation by Chauncey Alexander, executive director of NASW: "The American Liberal: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow" (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - National Economic Growth and Reconstruction Organization (NEGRO) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - National Paraplegia Foundation - New York Metropolitan Chapter (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - National Public Employees Fringe Benefits Conference (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness - Managing the Volunteer Organization Seminar (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - National Welfare Rights Organization (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Nationwide Communications Network (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - New Alliances for Brooklyn (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - New Professionals Symposium (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - New York City Alliance of Community Sponsored Agencies (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - New York Association for Brain Injured Children (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - New York City Council on Economic Education (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - New York City Unemployed and Welfare Council (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - New York Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - New York Consumer Assembly (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - New York Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - New York School of Social Work Alumni Association (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - New York State Association for Human Services (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - New York State Association for Human Services - 79th Annual Conference (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - New York State Welfare Conference (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - New York University Graduate School of Social Work (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - New York Urban Coalition (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - New York Urban League (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Notes (Box 15, Folder 45-52)
  - Ocean Hill Alliance for Progress - Welfare League (Box 15, Folder 53)